

BART T. SITEK バート シーテック



Technical Lead/Sr. Architect, with vast prior experience in Full-Stack Web Development - namely designing, building and deploying web solutions. **12+ year industry experience**, of which 6 years in Tōkyō, Japan. Interested in (preferably) technical Director/VP/C-level opportunities.

For more information email hello@bar.tk or/and visit the website at bar.tk

MODULE 1.0
WORK EXPERIENCE

Q CO.,LTD. 【株式会社キュー】

TECHNICAL LEAD / SR. ARCHITECT

MAY 2017 - PRESENT

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Helping hit major milestones for the Adidas Online Store Japan project. Conducted feasibility study, architected and implemented foundation for the renewal prototype of the storefront using modern web technologies such as React, Next.js, MobX.
- Leading infra related efforts; serving as a "go-to" person for solving engineering issues and planning. Introducing new technologies (Docker, Kubernetes etc.) to the stack. Introducing, developing and integrating in-house tools tailored for specific company needs.
- Managing a team of junior developers, maintaining source code repositories and introducing workflows.

AVINTON

JAN 2015 - MAY 2017

HEAD OF FRONT END ENGINEERING

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Focusing on reliability, performance and security. Dramatically reduced app's loading times (~2.14s → 687ms) as well as bandwidth overhead (~1.2MB → 5.5KB) through implementation of effective server-side compression and client-side caching techniques.
 Developed a robust Big Data (tenths of millions of rows) harvesting platform and engineered a solution for it, which drastically improved its scalability and performance.
- Managing a team of junior developers and maintaining source code repositories. Providing guidance and introducing contractors to company system and workflows.
- Involved in making strategic decisions regarding company products and actively introducing new tools and processes in order to optimize workflows.
- Architecting and maintaining a proprietary Single Page Application framework built from the grounds up in-house and targeted at major Telecom clients. Introducing cutting edge technologies to the stack and making sure it stays up to date and up to spec.

MODULE 1.1
WORK EXPERIENCE

CEREGO JAPAN (DMM英会話)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (FRONT END) & DESIGNER

MAR 2014 - DEC 2014

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Working directly with the Head of Product on establishing a brand new modern feel for the service
- Responsible for UI/UX prototyping, designing and developing front-end for the core areas of the service (Memory Bank, Dashboard, Course Directory & Listing etc.)
- Designing and maintaining wireframes, templates & other assets.

ANYDOOR K.K.

NOV 2012 - MAR 2014

UI/UX & FRONT END DIRECTOR

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Worked in a team to build and launch Conyac Business platform that is now core service.
- Directly responsible for prototyping & building front-end for the Conyac Business platform. Helped establishing corporate branding guidelines.
- Responsible for introducing many new technologies to the business to improve workflow and application performance.

 $B \land R T \equiv K$

NOV 1985 - PRESENT

FOUNDER / AUTHOR

EARTH AND BEYOND

- Created Projector, a tool for easy template/project sharing. It ended up on the first page of HackerNews, featured on SmashingMagazine, Script of the Day on Softpedia and generated several thousand downloads within few days.
- Launched in 2011, Instatrip is a web service allowing people to automatically group Instagram photos into trips and puts them on a beautifully crafted map. Service created a lot of buzz and has been officially used by then-President of Costa Rica Laura Chinchilla to map out her trips.
- Launched in 2010, SECURO makes it possible to find out what's happening around you at any given time. By taking a look at the radar map one can find out about traffic accidents, promotions and maybe even about a newly opened store. Service was targeting users based in Japan.
- Started in 2006, βetateam group is devoted to making technology better by testing and reviewing IT related products, including websites and web services. βetateam is a valued partner of top tech companies such as Microsoft, Intel, Hewlett-Packard, Seagate, Orange. Certificates available upon request.
- Prior to founding βetateam I was involved in testing and providing feedback for core Microsoft products such as: Windows Vista, Microsoft Update, Internet Explorer, Windows XP Media Center Edition and many others. I was also testing and reviewing products for Plantronics (audio equipment), Netgear (unmanageable and manageable switches, routers and other network peripherals), Symantec (antivirus solutions), Kingston Technology (newest line of pen drives at the time) and many more.

MODULE 2.0
EDUCATION

WARSAW SCHOOL OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

M.S., IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT

2009 - DROPPED OUT WARSAW, POLAND

WARSAW SCHOOL OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

2005 - 2009

B.S., COMPUTER SCIENCE (MULTIMEDIA)

WARSAW, POLAND

MODULE 3.0 ACHIEVEMENTS

2019

- Algorithms: Design and Analysis, Stanford Online
- Compilers, Stanford Online

2014

• E-Skills Ambassador, Grand Coalition for Digital Jobs, European Commission

2010

• NASA Subsonic Rotary Wing Project technical paper: "VECTOR: Conceptual Design of Amphibious Tiltrotor for Rescue Operations" (PDF download); ISSN 1819-6608

2009

- Honorable Mention, NASA Art & Design Contest
- Certified Trainer, Cisco Demo Lounge

2007

- MicroStrategy Business Intelligence Engineer
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional, Charter Member (MCITP): Desktop Support -Enterprise
- Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist, Charter Member (MCTS): Windows Vista Client, Configuring
- Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP)